<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ini-Resep</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="recipes_fragment">Recipes</string>
    <string name="favorite_recipes_fragment">Favorites</string>
    <string name="food_joke_fragment">Tips Cook</string>

    // Bottom Sheet
    <string name="meal_type">Meal Type</string>
    <string name="main_course">Main Course</string>
    <string name="side_dish">Side Dish</string>
    <string name="dessert">Dessert</string>
    <string name="appetizer">Appetizer</string>
    <string name="salad">Salad</string>
    <string name="bread">Bread</string>
    <string name="breakfast">Breakfast</string>
    <string name="soup">Soup</string>
    <string name="beverage">Beverage</string>
    <string name="sauce">Sauce</string>
    <string name="marinade">Marinade</string>
    <string name="fingerfood">FingerFood</string>
    <string name="snack">Snack</string>
    <string name="drink">Drink</string>
    <string name="ketogenic">Ketogenic</string>
    <string name="pescetarian">Pescetarian</string>
    <string name="paleo">Paleo</string>
    <string name="primal">Primal</string>
    <string name="whole30">Whole30</string>
    <string name="diet_type">Diet Type</string>
    <string name="apply">Apply</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="save_to_favorites">Save To Favorite Menu</string>
    <string name="no_favorite_recipes">No Favorite Recipes</string>

    <string name="vegetarian">Vegetarian</string>
    <string name="vegan">Vegan</string>
    <string name="gluten_free">Gluten Free </string>
    <string name="cheap">Cheap</string>
    <string name="healthy">Healthy</string>
    <string name="dairy_free">Dairy Free</string>
    <string name="delete_favorite_menu">Delete Favorite Menu</string>
    <string name="delete_all">Delete All</string>


    <string name="hacks_cook">KITCHEN HACKS AND COOKING TIPS</string>
    <string name="hacks1">There’s nothing worse than stale bread. What happens, though, if you don’t
        have time to run to the store to buy a fresh loaf? Looks like you’re stuck with a stale baguette.
        Or are you? Maybe not! Try running the bread under some water and stick it in the oven for 5 to 10 minutes.
        You can also wrap it in a damp paper towel and pop it in the oven. With this little hack, your
        bread will come out fresh and crunchy as if you had just baked it!</string>
    <string name="hacks2">Pancakes are often viewed as a guilty pleasure, something you
        indulge in on special occasions, right? We often see healthy pancakes at cafes and breakfast
        boutiques, but you can make your own version at home! If you’re having a lazy morning and you’re
        in the mood for this special breakfast treat, you can make a healthy diet-friendly version. You
        can use protein powder, almond milk, oat flour, fruit, dried fruit as substitutes for the fatty
        ingredients – it’s that simple!</string>
    <string name="hacks3">We’ve all been in the scenario when we’ve boiled an egg, but when we try
        and peel it, all that is left is less than half of the egg. If you let the eggs cool off,
        they’ll be much easier to peel. If you’re really in the mood for eating the boiled eggs the
        moment they’re done cooking, you can add a little salt in the water when they cook. When
        they’re done – use a spoon to crack one end slightly and peel the shell from the inside!</string>
    <string name="hacks4">If eggs are stored properly, they can usually last for three to five weeks.
        Still, it’s better to be safe than sorry. After all, no one likes cracking open a rotten egg,
        especially if they’re planning to cook with it. To ensure that this doesn’t happen to you,
        pop the egg into a large bowl or glass of cold water. If the little guy sinks, you’re good
        to go. If it floats, throw it away and buy yourself some fresh eggs!</string>
    <string name="hacks5">Squeezing lemons is a hard task, especially if you thought you were cutting
        open a juicy lemon, and you realize it’s not! You can get more juice from a lemon by microwaving
        it on high for about 20 seconds. It sounds crazy, we know, but it works! It will become softer
        than a lemon straight from the fridge, making the citrus fruit much easier to squeeze.
        Next time you’re stuck with a tough lemon, try this!</string>


</resources>